Aaron Parisi

Web Developer

I am a Web Developer based in Seattle, WA, with a passion for building web applications that even my parents could use. It started when I taught Multivariable Calculus on a whiteboard. A few years later, I worked at a real estate exchange company where I spent my free time writing Excel macros and AutoHotKey scripts to create organizational tools which could actually help me in my day-to-day work. I realized I want to build web applications that feel easy, work well, and look stunning.

parisi.aaron@gmail.com

518.573.3522

Seattle, WA

www.aaronparisidev.com 🥽

linkedin.com/in/aaron-parisi in

github.com/aaronparisi

stackoverflow.com/users/5221310/aaron-parisi

EDUCATION

Fullstack Web Development AppAcademy Open

05/2020 - 02/2021

- Object Oriented Design in Rubv

 Data Structures & Basic Algorithms

Hartwick College

Discrete Mathematics

1031 Services, Inc. 09/2018 - 02/2020

exchanges in the country.

Abstract Algebra

- Number Theory

09/2010 - 05/2014

Courses

- Functional & Asynchronous Programming in JavaScript

 Frontend State Management using Redux

BA Mathematics, BA Economics (Honors)

Seattle, WA

3.9 / 4.0

- Database Design with MySQL and PostgreSQL

RESTful applications using Rails, MVC paradigm

Linear Algebra

Real Analysis

- Frontend Rendering in React

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Springfield BnB

- Built with a React+Redux frontend and a Rails API, this Simpsons-themed Air BnB clone features AWS S3 image storage & frontend authentication
- Configured API to accept CORS requests from both local and live frontends
- Addressed AWS configuration and secret key exposure
- Deployed backend to Heroku and frontend to Firebase

Candie's Swingin' 70th Birthday Bash

- Improved upon a Wix birthday info site for a friend
- Simplified the costume ideas page with sliders for genre and gender, maintaining state of functional React components
- Addressed navbar visibility against hero video playback by examining the underlying HTML element's data attributes

Todos

- Bundled a standard Todos app with Webpacker and some customizations to package.json
- Blended some Rails html.erb views with pure React components
- Made database queries using Axios and ES6 promise syntax

Jeerkat Clock

The clock you didn't know you needed, this vanilla JavaScript project features a simple drag-and-drop timeline and some funky background-color animations

Towers of Hanoi + Demo

 Pause, rewind, modify, and continue the demo that relies on plenty of ES6 promise syntax, or just play around with the intuitive mouseover features of this jQuery rendition of the classic game

 Managed 30+ 1031 real estate exchanges, facilitating the transfer of hundreds of thousands of dollars in real estate proceeds

One of the most experienced and reliable facilitators of 1031 tax-deferred

Computer Science Tutor

WORK EXPERIENCE

Legal Administrative Assistant

Northeastern University Seattle

09/2017 - 12/2017

Tutored grad students in Intro to Functional Programming at Northeastern University's Seattle campus

High School Mathematics Teacher Salisbury School

09/2014 - 05/2015

A private, all-boys boarding school in northwest Connecticut

Taught Advanced Placement Calculus BC, Multivariable Calculus, and Probability & Statistics to high school juniors and seniors

INTERESTS

Web Design

Animation

Meditation

Yoga

Cycling